

# JUAN PABLO ROMANO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & DEVOPS ENGINEER

GITHUB: JPROMANONET | JPROMANO.NET

# **PROFILE**

I am a full stack developer with robust problem-solving skills and more than 9 years of proven experience in creating and designing software solutions for different companies.

## HOW TO REACH ME

Cell: +54-9-11-2180-5256 Email: iromano@matelab.com.ar

LinkedIn: @jupromano Twitter: @juanpromano

# **SKILLS**

#### **Coding Languages**

Python, Javascript, NodeJS, Jquery, Ajax, HTML5 & CSS3, PHP, C, C#, C++, Bash, Batch, Ruby, Perl, Lisp, COBOL, QuickBasic, Pascal, Visual Basic, ASP Classic, ASP.NET, ASP.Net Core, R, Java, Django, Golang, Ruby on Rails, JSP, Assembler, .NET Framework, ReactJS, VueJS, AngularJS

## **Databases**

Microsoft SQL(2005. 2008, 2016, 2019), MySQL, MongoDB, GraphQL, I-SQL, T-SQL, CosmoDB, PostgreSQL

#### **Operative Systems**

Linux(Ubuntu, RedHat, Debian), Unix, Windows 10, Windows Server 2008, Windows Server 2012, Windows Server 2016, BSD

# CAREER SUMMARY

**Technical Lead - Matelab**November 2019 to present

Expert Tutor - Teclab Institute June 2021 to August 2021

DevOps Engineer - Globant September 2020 to April 2021

Full Stack Developer - El Cronista Comercial September 2018 to September 2020

Full Stack Developer - Healthy SA September 2017 to September 2018

Full Stack Developer - Accusys Technology December 2015 to September 2017

Full Stack Developer - AG S.A November 2012 to December 2015

# **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**

National University of Lomas de Zamora Degree in Information Technology Management

• 2021 to Present

National University of Lomas de Zamora Under degree in Software Development

• 2019 to 2021

University of Buenos Aires Degree in Mathematics

• 2013 to 2017

### COURSES

#### University of Helsinski

• Java - Object Oriented Programming

#### Acamica

- Introduction to the Technical Leader's Role
- The Basics of Customer Centricity
- · Web Accesibility
- · Harnessing the Power of AI
- Diversity and Inclusion

#### SoloLearn

- PHP Course
- Data Science with Python
- Machine Learning Certification
- C# Certificate
- Javascript Certificate
- HTML5 Certificate
- C++ Tutorial Course
- · Python 3 Course
- · C Certificate
- SQL Fundamentals
- Java Certificate

### Free Code Camp

- Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures
- · APIs and Microservices
- Data Visualization
- Frontend Libraries
- Information Security and Quality Assurance
- Responsive Web Design

#### Educación IT

- Linux User
- Linux Operator
- · Advanced Linux Hosting Administrator
- Linux Networks Introduction
- Databases and SQL Introduction
- Linux Introduction
- SQL Programming Fundamentals
- Linux Administrator
- · Linux Shell Scripting
- Advanced Linux Networks
- · Server Hacking with Linux

#### Microsoft

- · Xamarin Certification
- ASP.NET Core

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Azure AZ400 - Azure DevOps

Microsoft | 2020 to 2021

Azure AZ104 - Azure Administrator

Microsoft | 2020 to 2021

**Full Stack Developer** 

Free Code Camp | 2018 to 2019

Full Stack Developer

Coder House | 2014 to 2015

Linux Professional Certificate(LPI)

Educación IT | 2013 to 2014

Certificate of Ethical Hacking(CEH)

Educación IT | 2013 to 2014

## LANGUAGES

English - Advanced(Business English Program)

French - Advanced(B2)

Russian - Advanced(C1)

Chinese - Advanced(HSK Level - C1)

Spanish - Native